Welcome to the basic tutorial on how to
use easy code.
Let's first just start off with the
language. So we'll start with Hello
World.
Play it. See Hello right here.
Now if I put print raw.
Of the world.You
get Hello World.
Can't do this though.
Because the print function only prints 1
space in front.So what you'll
do is you use.
Space character which is a back slash.
Back slash and then this so print it and
it prints hello world like this.
So that's just kind of how the language
works. It's divided by spaces.
So next thing we'll do.As
we'll make a small little project.
All right. So first we'll print.
Draw.
Welcome to the mold.
Case in table.
Prince Royal.
Please enter a number to generate.
Right. And you see these?
Now we'll add a variable, so that's the
var.And
call it number.And it will be
read by console input.
So now the test will just print number.
This will do is it'll wait for you to
input.
And it and it prints right here.
That's just a test now.
What we'll need to do is.
Creates A variable named.
R in.And we'll sign it
to number. This will be the resetting
variable. This will set number back.
You you'll see in a second.So
now we'll create a
variable to.
That will be printed.That has the
inputted number, so we'll have what's
called text.
Undo text.
Yes.
Number.
Text Plus.
Pulling tanks.
Plus.
Text.Now we put in our
number.And multiplication
table for five 4.5.
Now what we'll do is.
We'll create some variables, so var
multiplier.
And it will be equal to
1 because that's the first number of
multiplication.Are
what's called a now, and
it'll be set to nothing and bar.
Results. Right now they'll just be set
to number.How about your
league 10 times?
Start by doing is
set number.T
ORN.
This will reset
the we'll use number later and this will
reset the numbers value back to the
original input.
Will make sure a is
equal to nothing again.
And we'll make results back to number.
So these just reset those 3 variables.
Now what we'll do is we'll do results
is equal is.
Multiplied by the multiplier.
And you'll see the multiplier will be
added. We'll add 1 to multiply.
Now in this loop.
And we will.
Prince results.
And so you see it will have This has
errors in it, but.This right here
has.The
multiplication table is now.We'll
finish this.I
put in.
Here's all spelled correctly.
Alright, we'll put.A
+ number.
A+ space.
8 plus.
Multiplier.A
plus.
Other space.8 plus.
Equals A plus.
Results.
And then we will.It's.
But what I'm through 9.
I forgot.
One more A+ space.
9.
A.
So that'll fix that, and then what is
the error that's happening?
So that fixes the.
Space is now What is the air that's
happening?
Right there.Groupon equal
sign.
Three enter So this is what we
have. Welcome welcome to the
multiplication table. Please enter your
number to generate multiplication
table for three. Then 3 * 1 three
3 * 2 six 3 * 3 is 9 and
so on.And then what we'll
do here is we'll put a nice
little thank you.
And there we go.Now
let's try using.
The visual output right here
we'll do is we'll create.
Text box.
Name it.
Text input.
So that's text and nothing. So now you
see we have this.
Visual output. We'll create a label and
we'll name it text.
OK, now we'll create.
Variable set to nothing right now.
And then we'll move.
Text output to label.
Below the.
Below the text box.
So we'll loop just pretty much forever.
And we will await every loop. We'll
wait 250 milliseconds per
second.
Now we will put our
equals.
Text and from
text box modifier
and then we'll put.
Textbox text input. So what this does is
it sets the variable text
to the to the.Input
of the text box, text input,
and then we'll end the loop.
One last thing I forgot.All
right.
Text input.
Output.
Now put in that.You
know, copy everything I put in there.
Now if I make.
Make.Text input
multiline and do this again.
They will also be multi lined.
So I hope this helps you understand the
basics of easy code and the syntax and
how it works.