OK, welcome to.The
store we're going to be learning how to
use easy code editor.
So I'll just go over each thing so this
has the top bar right here.This
has all of these. This is the main
navigation for this IDE.
This is the project list.This will
have.You can have a bunch of files right
here and go between them easily.
This is the visualizer output.
Or box?
Um, this is the
console. This is the console input so
where you can send it and this is what
clears the console.This is the
debugger. This will show all of the
variables when you align by line. We'll
get to that later.So we'll just
start with.
And you can see here it prints it right
there.Good.
Label high.Doesn't
print it out right there, but it will
put it right here. So this is the
visual, this is the console.
Um.We'll go
with this first. So this has
an auto save function. This will save
every time you type. Every time you type
a key on the keyboard it saves the file.
This will save the file. This opens file
new pretty self-explanatory undo
redo.This can
open a project list, so a project
list will store.
Files inside of here, so let me.
Add some files to there.
Here's some files so we can quickly go
between them. We'll put on autosave.
And we can quickly go between.
Different files.
And if I save this project list, it'll
save it to a file that I can
then open up later, and then I can
also remove a file from the list. So
this will start with an index, this being
01234.
If I put in two it should remove the
plaque click dot Easy code.And it does
so.Then you have
auto open project so this.
This has a.
It's putting a you are a a file URL or a
file directory right here
and every time you open up the editor
it'll open up this. If you want it to
stop doing that you can clear project
list.And it'll be empty again
and also package which will open up the
easy code packaging.We we won't need to
do that. Now that's pretty self-
explanatory too.So this is the
debug function if I
put let me create a small script real
quick.
We go, we go into debug.
So right here it shows the line
that we're on.Next line
has var a hello.And it
puts this right here so a is equal to
hello and then it has print A and then
right here you can see.Next
line.Says high in the hell
what it should do, but you can do it
line by line. That's how the debugger
works. So this is the quid debugger and
next line.You also play it all at
once.Which will just play it
immediately, stop it and play in viewer.
This will open up the easy code viewer.
And.Already to this file, but that's
also pretty self-explanatory. We won't
go over that.This will
open up the docks.
Um for on the easy code
website and then this will show you all
the hot keys.And go over that
either.That is.
Pretty much it this will one more thing
and here if you have objects and labels,
this will show all the objects it's
positions and stuff as values. This will
show all the labels, its positions and
values.And so
that's it for the easy code editor.
Hope you learned something from this.