OK, welcome to this soil. We're going to
learn how to use easy cooked packager.
So.First things
first.You have to get your
project directory.So I'm going to open
folder.And my project
directory directory is right there.
So
Second step is open your startup
file.Startup
file is.Right
there.Then your
output folder, I'm going to output it to
desktop.Alright, I'm gonna
leave the author unknown, but the
company is.
Beavers Development.
Package might call it.
Alright, package
successfully packaged, so now we can
exit out of that.And here it is.
OK, so if you also have your project.
On Easy Code you can
click Package and I'll ask you if it's
installed.I haven't installed
and you find the directory.
And it'll open it up.
Alright, that's it. Hope you learned.