Alright, welcome to This Tutorial. Now
we'll learn how to use Easy Codes
Project Player.So.
It's very straightforward. You have
open, exit, you play and stop
toggle errors. What this will do is if
there's an error in the code.This will
toggle if you want to see it or not. So
on and off. This is the version and this
is the language.This is.
You can either show the console space
plus console or space.
But you can also just use this to move
it around. This will show the author and
company and this right here will show
the.Um.
Show the file directory. So let's open a
file.
Open.
Let's open this one.
And play it.So this is a.
It's not a console game, so we'll put it
right here.This is something I
made. Um.
Just put a name.Play it.
There's nothing really.
Pretty much the entire thing. There's
nothing to it.So.
That is that is it for this. Hope you
learned something and.