In the straw we will learn how to use
Easy Code Viewer.Pretty pretty
simple. So you have an
open, we'll open a file, exit, so
Start Stop and this just shows the
viewer and then the languages version.
This is the visualizer box.
This is the.Console
and this is the console input and that's
the send button.What we'll do here
is we'll open a file.
Open up pong, for example.
And what play?
And it'll take your input.
And it'll play it.Account for
teacher.And we'll just
stop this for now.
If you have a program that takes.
Sorry, this took a second to find the
file. Um, we can move this
up.And this
is the multiplication generator after
that.And it worked just like this.
It's pretty straightforward. Now this
works. There's one more thing though, if
we move this go into here.
And you want to play a file in the
viewer.Versus open file.
We will open Pong.
And we put Play play viewer.
It will open up the viewer with it
already loaded in.And if it's your first
time doing it.And it'll ask you
questions, and it'll ask you.
And if it's your first time doing it,
it'll ask you where.
If you haven't installed and where it is
located.And then
every time after that it'll
automatically open it for you.
So.That
is, that is it for this video. Hope you
learned something.